<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kamera</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <name>Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKameraxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kamera</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Kamera</name>
  <summary>A plugin to support Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) in KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="az">KDE tətbiqlərində Şəkil Köçürmə Protokolu (PTP) dəstəkləyən əlavə</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un connector per a admetre el protocol de transferència d'imatges (Picture Transfer Protocol -PTP-) a les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un connector per a admetre el protocol de transferència d'imatges (Picture Transfer Protocol -PTP-) a les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Modul für das Bildaustauschprotokoll  (PTP) in KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ένα πρόσθετο για υποστήριξη του πρωτοκόλλου μεταφοράς εικόνων (PTP) στις εφαρμογές του KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A plugin to support Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) in KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un complemento para usar el protocolo de transferencia de imágenes (PTP) en aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Plugin, mis pakub pildiedastuse protokolli PTP toetust KDE rakendustes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDE aplikazioetan Irudien Transferentziarako Protokoloari (PTP) euskarri emateko plugin bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">PTP-yhteyskäytäntöä (Picture Transfer Protocol) tukeva liitännäinen KDE-sovelluksiin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un module externe de prise en charge du protocole de transfert d'images (PTP) au sein des applications KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Un complemento para permitir o protocolo de transferencia de imaxes (PTP) nas aplicacións de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Un plugin pro supportar Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) in applicationes de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un'estensione per supportare la modalità Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) nelle applicazioni di KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램에서 사진 전송 프로토콜(PTP)을 지원하는 플러그인</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Papildinys, skirtas "Picture Transfer Protocol" (PTP) protokolo palaikymui KDE programose</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een plug-in om Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) in KDE-toepassingen te ondersteunen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Programtillegg for å støtta PTP (Picture Transfer Protocol) i KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wtyczka do obsługi Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) w aplikacjach KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um 'plugin' que suporta o protocolo Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) nas aplicações do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um plugin que tem suporte ao protocolo Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) nos aplicativos do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Extensie pentru susținerea Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) în aplicații KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Подключаемый модуль поддержки протокола передачи изображений (Picture Transfer Protocol, PTP) для приложений KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Plugin na podporu protokolu PTP v KDE aplikáciách</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Vtičnik za podporo protokola za prenos slike (PTP) v aplikacijah KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett insticksprogram för att stödja bildöverföringsprotokollet (Picture Transfer Protocol, PTP) i KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Додаток для підтримки протоколу передавання зображень (PTP) у програмах KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA plugin to support Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) in KDE applicationsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在 KDE 应用程序中支持图片传输协议 (PTP) 的插件</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">用來在 KDE 應用程式支援影像傳輸協定 (PTP) 的外掛程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) is an older method of talking to camera devices.  Kamera provides a configuration tool and kio slave to read and write to camera devices with this protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="az">Şəkil Köçürmə Protokolu (ing. - PTP) kamera ilə işləmək üçün köhnə üsuldur. Kamera tətbiqi, bu protokol vasitəsi ilə kamera cihazlarına yazmaq və oxumaq üçün ayarlar aləti təqdim edir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El protocol de transferència d'imatges (PTP) és un mètode antic de parlar amb els dispositius de càmera. El Kamera proporciona una eina de configuració i un esclau kio per a llegir i escriure als dispositius de càmera amb aquest protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El protocol de transferència d'imatges (PTP) és un mètode antic de parlar amb els dispositius de càmera. El Kamera proporciona una eina de configuració i un esclau kio per a llegir i escriure als dispositius de càmera amb aquest protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Bildaustauschprotokoll (PTP) ist eine ältere Methode, um mit Kamerageräten zu kommunizieren. Kamera stellt ein Einrichtungsmodul und ein Ein-/Ausgabemodul zum Lesen und Schreiben auf Kamerageräten mit diesem Protokoll zur Verfügung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το πρωτόκολλο μεταφοράς εικόνων (PTP) είναι μία παλαιότερη μέθοδος επικοινωνίας με κάμερες. Η Kamera παρέχει ένα εργαλείο διαμόρφωσης και kio slave για ανάγνωση και εγγραφή συσκευών κάμερας με αυτό το πρωτόκολλο.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) is an older method of talking to camera devices. Kamera provides a configuration tool and kio slave to read and write to camera devices with this protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El protocolo de transferencia de imágenes (PTP) es un método antiguo de dialogar con dispositivos de cámara. Kamera proporciona una herramienta de configuración y un esclavo «kio» para leer y escribir en dispositivos de cámara mediante este protocolo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Pildiedastuse protokoll PTP on juba eakas kaameraseadmetega suhtlemise viis. Kamera pakub seadistamistööriista ja KIO-moodulit kaameraseadmete lugemiseks ja neisse kirjutamiseks selle protokolli abil.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Irudien Transferentziarako Protokoloa (PTP) kamera gailuei hitz egiteko metodo zaharrago bat da. Kamerak protokolo hau darabilten kamerak konfiguratzeko tresna bat eskaintzen du baita haietan irakurtzeko eta idazteko kio morroi bat ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">PTP (Picture Transfer Protocol) on vanhempi yhteyskäytäntö kameralaitteiden käyttämiseksi. Kamera tarjoaa tälle yhteyskäytännölle asetustyökalun ja kio-asiakkaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le protocole de transfert d'images (PTP) est une ancienne méthode de communication avec les appareils photo. Kamera fournit un outil de configuration et un esclave kio permettant de lire et d'écrire vers les appareils photo utilisant ce protocole.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O protocolo de transferencia de imaxes (PTP) é un método antigo de comunicación con dispositivos de cámara. Kamera fornece unha ferramenta de configuración e un escravo de KIO para ler e escribir datos de dispositivos de cámara con este protocolo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) es un vetere methodo de parlar a dispositivos de camera. Kamera forni un instrumento de configuration e kio slave per scriber a iste dispositivos con iste protocollo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) è un vecchio metodo usato per dialogare con le fotocamere. Kamera fornisce uno strumento di configurazione e uno slave KIO per eseguire con questo protocollo le operazioni di lettura e di scrittura sulle fotocamere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">사진 전송 프로토콜(PTP)은 이전 세대 카메라 장치와 통신하는 방식입니다. Kamera는 PTP 설정 도구 및 이 프로토콜을 지원하는 카메라 장치에서 읽기 및 쓰기를 할 수 있는 KIO 슬레이브를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">"Picture Transfer Protocol" (PTP) yra senesnis bendravimo su fotoaparatais būdas. Kamera pateikia konfigūravimo įrankį ir kio pavaldųjį, skirtą skaityti ir rašyti į fotoaparato įrenginius naudojant šį protokolą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) is een oudere methode voor praten met camera-apparaten. Kamera biedt een hulpmiddel voor configuratie en kio-slave om te lezen en te schrijven van/naar camera-apparaten met dit protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">PTP (Picture Transfer Protocol) er ein eldre metode for kommunikasjon med kameraeiningar. Programmet har eit oppsettverktøy og ein KIO-slave for å lesa frå og skriva til kameraeiningar med denne protokollen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) jest starszym sposobem na nawiązywanie łączności z aparatami. Kamera zapewnia narzędzie do ustawiania oraz kio slave do odczytywania i zapisywania na aparaty przy użyciu tego narzędzia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O protocolo Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) é um método mais antigo de comunicação com dispositivos de câmaras. O Kamera oferece uma ferramenta de configuração e um 'kio slave' para ler e escrever nos dispositivos de câmaras com este protocolo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O protocolo Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) é um método mais antigo de comunicação com dispositivos de câmera. O Kamera fornece uma ferramenta de configuração e um 'kio slave' para ler e gravar nos dispositivos de câmera com este protocolo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) e o metodă mai veche de comunicare cu dispozitive fotografice. Kamera oferă o unealtă de configurare și un sclav KIO pentru citirea și scrierea pe dispozitive fotografice cu acest protocol.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Протокол передачи изображений (Picture Transfer Protocol, PTP) — ранний способ получения изображений с камер. Модуль поддержки камер предоставляет инструмент для настройки и модуль файловой системы для чтения и записи изображений камеры с использованием этого протокола.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Picture Transfer Protocol (PTP) je staršou metódou komunikácie s kamerovými zariadeniami. Kamera poskytuje konfiguračný nástroj a kio slave na čítanie a zápis do kamerových zariadení pomocou tohto protokolu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Protokol za prenos slike (PTP) je starejši način komunikacije s foto napravami. Kamera ponuja orodje za nastavitve in kio odjemalca za branje in pisanje na foto naprave s tem protokolom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Bildöverföringsprotokollet (Picture Transfer Protocol, PTP) är en äldre metod för att kommunicera med kameraenheter. Kamera tillhandahåller ett inställningsverktyg och I/O-slav för att läsa och skriva till kameraenheter med protokollet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Протокол передавання зображень (PTP) є застарілим способом обміну даними із пристроями для знімання зображень. Kamera є інструментом налаштовування та підлеглим засобом введення-виведення даних для читання і запису даних на основі цього протоколу.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxPicture Transfer Protocol (PTP) is an older method of talking to camera devices. Kamera provides a configuration tool and kio slave to read and write to camera devices with this protocol.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">图片传输协议 (PTP) 是一个用于和照相机设备进行通讯的较老的协议。Kamera 提供了一个配置工具，及一个 kio slave，用于以此协议来读写照相机设备。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">影像傳輸協定 (PTP) 是個與相機裝置溝通的舊方法。Kamera 提供了設定工具及 KIO Slave 來使用此協定讀取及寫入相機裝置。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=systemsettings</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kcontrol%2Fkamera</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kamera/kamera.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">camera-photo</icon>
</component>
